[gentle serene music] Before we pray,
I would like to say
a few words, and then we will pray
together. There are countless things
that can go wrong in your
day if you choose not to begin it with
prayer.
Of course, challenges
and difficulties can still arise
even when you do pray in the morning.
However, the difference is
that starting your day with prayer
brings a peace that surpasses human
understanding.
When you pray, there
is a special grace upon you.
You're able to handle situations with
confidence because you know that you
have a God who is working through you,
in you, and for you.
God already knows what we will face each
day before we even open our
eyes.
So why not take a few moments to connect
guidance?
Why not spend a little time asking for His
direction?
Why not take a moment to ask for His
protection?
Taking those few moments to pray can make
difference in how you handle the ups
and downs of the day.
Let's pray together.
Dear Lord, I come before you today
and place this
entire day into your loving hands.
I ask for your wonderful grace,
your calming peace, and your
strong protection to be with me throughout
every moment of this
day.
Please guide me away from any temptations
wrong paths that might come my way.
Give me the strength
and the grace to keep my heart pure
anything that isn't good for me
or pleasing to you.
Lord,
I ask that you take control of my heart.
Help me manage my emotions
and thoughts so that they stay focused on
is right and true.
Let your presence be so real and clear
to me today that I have no reason to fear
anything.
Instead,
help me walk confidently with complete
you, the God of the heavens,
are watching over me.
I pray that nothing can separate me from
you today.
Teach me how to follow your ways
and make the right choices so that every
step I take leads me closer to you.
I want to feel your love
surrounding me and be aware of your
powerful presence in everything I
do and everywhere I go. I ask for the
protection of Jesus' blood to cover me
and my family.
May your divine pillar of fire be seen
where my family and I live each
night,
forming a protective barrier around us
safe from all harm. Father, I pray for a
hedge of protection around me at my job,
and I ask for your divine
protection as I travel in my car. Lord
Jesus,
please surround me with your love and
safety. Give me the strength
and courage to face whatever
this day may bring. Lord,
I don't know what
challenges or opportunities lie ahead
today, but I trust that you will
be with me every step of the way.
Please guide my steps today in a direction
that leads to peace and
happiness. Strengthen my heart so
that I can follow your
commandments and walk in obedience to your
Word.
I ask for your grace
and mercy to guide me from heaven,
wise choices. You are my provider,
my Jehovah
Jireh.
You are the one who makes a way
way. Be my strong tower, my protector, and
my master. I ask for peace of mind
and peace within my
heart. Help me to stay calm and focused,
no matter what
happens. Father, I have faith that you
are working
everything together for my good.
Please silence every
confusing or negative voice from the
enemy.
You are a God who loves us so much,
and even when you are working
behind the scenes in ways I cannot see
or understand, I will
continue to trust you.
I will keep my faith strong because your
ways are higher and greater than ours.
Protect me from any selfish
or careless thoughts, words, or actions
that don't bring glory to you.
Keep me from being distracted
or discouraged by the devil.
Shield me from the influence of any
negative or discouraging
people. Help me to stay positive
and focused on
you. Father, I am so thankful for the
gift of this new day. Waking up
and having the
chance to start fresh is such a blessing.
I am filled with joy
and gratitude for this opportunity.
May your presence, Lord,
shine brightly in my life today
and set my heart on fire with love for
you, Jesus.
Let your light guide me
and fill me with passion and
devotion. Father, I ask
that you open doors for
me today. Open doors of opportunity
that will lead to positive
changes and breakthroughs in my life.
Show me the paths I should take,
and give me the courage to step through
doors with confidence. Help me to see
and seize the
opportunities you place before me.
Lord, help me to walk by faith
and not just by
what I see around me.
Teach me to trust in your Word and
promises,
even when things seem uncertain or
challenging.
Help me to rely on your truth and not be
swayed by my feelings or circumstances.
I commit myself and my family into your
loving and protective hands.
Watch over us and guide us throughout this
day.
Keep us safe,
and help us to stay close to you in
do. In the name of Jesus,
I bless your holy
name. I am grateful for your endless love,
grace, and
mercy.
Thank you for always being there for us
our lives in ways we can't always see.
In Jesus' name, I pray. Amen.
If this prayer
has touched your heart, please type amen.
I pray that every blessing in this prayer
is now upon you in the name of
Jesus. May the grace
and peace of our Lord Jesus Christ be with
all.