[gentle music]
Good morning, Lord. Today's a new day,
a chance for a new start. Yesterday is
gone, and with it, any regrets,
mistakes, or failures
I may have experienced.
It's a good day to be glad
and give thanks, and I do, Lord.
Thank you for today,
a new opportunity to love,
give, and be all that you want me to be.
Today, I want to start the day
with you on my mind and in my heart.
As I dress,
let me wear the armor you've provided
daily: the helmet of
salvation,
the breastplate of righteousness,
the shield of faith, the belt of truth,
the
shoes of peace,
and the sword of the spirit, with
prayer on my tongue, praise for you, and
petitions for those around me
and those I meet.
Feed me today with your daily bread.
As the bread of life, your food,
like manna,
will sustain me throughout any trials
and hungers.
Help me to set my thoughts on things above
and to
speak only what will help and encourage
others.
Keep me from putting my foot in my mouth
and help me guard the affections of my
heart today, Lord.
Make whatever work I do be marked with
excellence rather than
perfectionism, as I seek not to make a
name, but to make a difference. Help me to
treat each person I encounter as you
would, with
respect and love, forgiving others
and asking for
forgiveness myself when needed.
As I start this
day, help me remember that I belong to
you, and my desire is to act accordingly.
Keep my feet from stumbling
and my mind from wandering
into distractions
that could steal precious time and energy
from the most important things you have
designed for me.
I'm proud to be your child, Lord,
and I'm so
grateful that you died for me,
rising again so that
every day could be filled with the wonder
of your love, the
freedom of your spirit,
and the joy of knowing
you. I know earthly life is short
and fleeting,
Lord, but I want to live today
as if it were the first
or the last day of my life,
giving thanks for every good
and perfect gift you choose to
give. Today, and every day, I want to
live my life for you, Jesus.
In your precious
name, I pray. Amen.
[gentle music]